http://www.natren.com/pages/privacy-policy

What probiotics are right for you?
About Probiotics
What are Probiotics?
What Are Prebiotics?
10 Surprising Benefits of Probiotics
6 Reasons You Should Be Very Cautious When Buying Cheaper Store-Bought Probiotics
5 Things to Know About Keeping Probiotics at the Right Temperature
Probiotics and Weight Loss
How Probiotics Can Boost Your Immune System
Prebiotics Vs. Probiotics
Are Probiotics Good For Babies?
Are Probiotics Good For Dogs?
Best Probiotic for Cats
Probiotics and Diarrhea?
+
What are Probiotics?
What Are Prebiotics?
10 Surprising Benefits of Probiotics
6 Reasons You Should Be Very Cautious When Buying Cheaper Store-Bought Probiotics
5 Things to Know About Keeping Probiotics at the Right Temperature
Probiotics and Weight Loss
How Probiotics Can Boost Your Immune System
Prebiotics Vs. Probiotics
Are Probiotics Good For Babies?
Are Probiotics Good For Dogs?
Best Probiotic for Cats
Probiotics and Diarrhea?
Sign in
We Are Open & Shipping As Usual.
Save 20% on Subscription Orders of $65 or More!
Privacy Policy
At Natren we're committed to protecting your right to privacy. In keeping with that commitment, we are providing you with the details about the information we collect while doing business.
Natren respects the privacy needs and concerns of our customers. That is how we handle any personal information, such as your name, address, email address or phone number ("Personal Information") that you provide to us is important to us. To earn your trust, we respect your privacy in handling Personal Information relating to you and your transactions with us. This Privacy Statement describes the Personal Information we gather about you, what we do with it, the safeguards we have in place to protect it, and how you can control our use of it. By using the Site, the user agrees, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Statement.When you provide Personal Information at our Site, you are consenting to the manner in which Natren will collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your Personal Information, as set out below.
Who May Use the Site?The Site are not intended or designed to attract users under the age of 18. We do not collect Personal Information from any person we know to be under the age of 18. If you are under 18, we ask that you not send us any Personal Information. The Sites are intended for users from the United States and those not governed by privacy policies of other countries. Do not send us information unless you consent to the application of U.S law and to the use and disclosure of your information consistent with this Privacy Statement.
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Site RegistrationRegistration is an optional service provided by our site. You do not have to register to browse our site, but you do have to register to purchase products on our site. When you register, you are asked for information such as your name, address, phone number and email address, and a password that you select. Your registration information is used to make your shopping experience quicker and easier. We do not keep your private information (credit cards) on file more than 60 days.
What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
To send periodic emails
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement ModificationsFrom time to time we may modify or amend this Privacy Statement in order to comply with new laws or regulations or to reflect future changes in our business practices. Any changes in our policies will be communicated in this page so please check back on occasion. We also may post a notice on our Site or send an email describing the changes.
Access to Personal InformationYou may request access to the Personal Information that we have about you. If you are a registered user with our Site, you can access your profile information at any time by clicking on the "Sign In/Register" link at the top of any page on the Site on which you registered.
Privacy Preferences / Opt-OutYou may change your marketing preferences or remove yourself from our mailing list by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in emails we send you or by contacting us at: Natren, Inc., Marketing Department – 3105 Willow Lane, Westlake Village, CA 91361. Please allow sufficient time for your preferences to be processed.
Additional Information about Our Site
Visiting Our SiteIn general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or providing us with any information. However, we collect the IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all visitors to our Sites and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our Sites. We use this information to monitor and improve our Site.
Cookies and Tracer TagsOur Sites use a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a tiny element of data that our Site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. All pages on our Site where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. If you have registered with our Site, these cookies (1) may let us know who you are, (2) are necessary to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver products and personalized services, and (3) will provide us and our Service Providers with information that we will use to personalize our Site in accordance with your preferences. Cookies are also required to optimize your shopping experience in that they allow you to add multiple items to your shopping basket before checking out. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. However, should you decide not to accept cookies from our Site, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Site.
We also use cookies to improve the performance of our advertising on other websites. Although you may not opt out of receiving online advertisements generally, you may control the collection of data on our site used for targeted Natren, Inc. advertising during your visits to other websites.
Tracer Tags: Our Sites may also use a technology called "tracer tags". These may also be referred to as "Clear GIFs" or "Web Beacons". This technology allows us to understand which pages you visit on our Site. These tracer tags are used to help us optimize and tailor our Site for you and other future website visitors.
Security of Personal InformationWe maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of Personal Information in our custody and control. We also are committed to employing reasonable technology in order to protect the security of our Site. However, even with the best technology, no website is 100% secure. We will take reasonable measures which we believe are appropriate to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction, and, where possible, will ask that any third parties to whom we may transfer such information to take comparable steps to protect that security.
Secure ShoppingWhen you place orders on our Site, all of your order information, including your card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology causes your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our secure server. SSL technology, an industry standard, is designed to prevent someone other than operators of our Site from capturing and viewing your Personal Information. Since any order information you provide to us on our Site will be transmitted using a secure connection, if your Web browser cannot support this level of security, you will not be able to order products through our Site. The most recent versions of Netscape Navigator™ and Microsoft Internet Explorer® can support a secure connection and can be downloaded for free from the Netscape and Microsoft website respectively.
PasswordsTo provide you with an increased level of security, online access to your Personal Information is protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. Natren, Inc. will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (including unsolicited correspondence such as letters, phone calls or e-mail messages).
Our Privacy Statement and Outside LinksThis Privacy Statement only applies to our site, www.natren.com. Our Site may include links to the websites of our business partners, vendors and advertisers. These other sites are outside of our control. Please be aware that these websites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices which may differ from those contained in our Privacy Statement. Remember to consult that website's own privacy policy, as once you are outside the www.natren.comSite, any information you submit is no longer in our control.
Contacting UsIf you have any questions about our handling of Personal Information, please contact us at Natren, Inc., 3105 Willow Lane, Westlake Village, CA 91361. Alternatively, you may call us toll-free at 1-800-992-3323.
Last Updated: April 21, 2014Copyright © 2014 Natren, Inc. All rights reserved
© Natren. All Rights Reserved. Designed & Developed By Studio III
Item successfully added to cart.
Continue Shopping
Go to Cart
